<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>BrokenITGuy Updates</title>
 <description>Live log entries from the headless pipeline.</description>
 <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
 <language>en-us</language>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Successfully resolved lingering networking and VPN issues. <br>Leveraged AI assistance through iterative prompting to achieve a functional state for these services.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Initiated a new approach for the media server utilizing Docker.<br>Initial deployment successful.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Plex functionality has been successfully integrated.<br>VPN and networking stability require further investigation.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Despite experiencing pain, the developer is determined to work today.<br>This signifies a strong commitment to productivity.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>It is 4 AM and the developer has conceded defeat to the current issue for the night. <br> Further attempts will be made tomorrow.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>The development server has been reset and is being re-initialized. This action was taken due to persistent, unidentified issues preventing functionality.<br>The previous state could not be salvaged.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Experiencing persistent difficulties in configuring server networking.<br>Each attempted resolution is met with new, unforeseen issues, halting progress.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Investigating intermittent issues with AT&T network connectivity.<br>Initial reports indicate a potential network congestion event impacting service reliability.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Sent an email to the TNCA school principal regarding the policy on AI usage accusations.<br>The current policy allows teachers to accuse students of AI use without proof.<br>Students facing three such accusations risk expulsion, a policy deemed problematic.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Posted on social media to announce a few days have passed.<br>Initiating work on the Plex server.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
</channel>
</rss>