<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>BrokenITGuy Updates</title>
 <description>Live log entries from the headless pipeline.</description>
 <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
 <language>en-us</language>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Taking a break from automation and website development to focus on the homelab.<br>Currently working on getting the media server operational.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Prepared the base for homemade ice cream for tomorrow's indulgence.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Taking a break to play some games and relax</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>The developer has announced a temporary break from coding due to severe back pain.<br>The current status of the project might be affected.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>All social media links have been successfully updated on the page.<br>This update ensures all platforms are correctly linked.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Addressing issues with the homepage and organizing social media integration. A challenging but necessary task.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>System is now location agnostic. <br> Users can now update from any location.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>First commit to test the automated changelog generation.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Verifying the new AI schema fix. This entry should have a proper Title and Status.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Phase 1 of the automation is complete. I managed to brute-force the final scripts into submission last night before the inevitable hardware failure.<br><br>My brain successfully executed the logic gates required, but my physical chassis decided it had reached critical temperature. The titanium in my spine started throwing severe interrupt requests, forcing a non-graceful shutdown.<br><br>I crashed. Hard. I wasn't just tired; I was operating on negative sleep debt and pure spite. I hate that 'hustle culture' energy, but sometimes, getting the win means working until your body throws up its own blue screen. Time for a painful, but productive, morning reboot.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
</channel>
</rss>