<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>BrokenITGuy Updates</title>
 <description>Live log entries from the headless pipeline.</description>
 <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
 <language>en-us</language>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>All social media links have been successfully updated on the page.<br>This update ensures all platforms are correctly linked.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Addressing issues with the homepage and organizing social media integration. A challenging but necessary task.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>System is now location agnostic. <br> Users can now update from any location.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>First commit to test the automated changelog generation.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Verifying the new AI schema fix. This entry should have a proper Title and Status.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Phase 1 of the automation is complete. I managed to brute-force the final scripts into submission last night before the inevitable hardware failure.<br><br>My brain successfully executed the logic gates required, but my physical chassis decided it had reached critical temperature. The titanium in my spine started throwing severe interrupt requests, forcing a non-graceful shutdown.<br><br>I crashed. Hard. I wasn't just tired; I was operating on negative sleep debt and pure spite. I hate that 'hustle culture' energy, but sometimes, getting the win means working until your body throws up its own blue screen. Time for a painful, but productive, morning reboot.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>The glorious moment of non-intervention. I have successfully convinced the new system (after several painful reboots and a few choice words aimed at the power supply) that it can, in fact, run without my constant supervision.<br><br>I’m closing the blast doors now. The process is self-sustaining. This is the delicate dance where I back away slowly, trusting that the uptime timer doesn't immediately roll over into an apocalyptic 0xFFFFFFFF error the moment my foot leaves the rack.<br><br>If it survives the next 12 hours, I might actually trust it. Emphasis on *might*.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>The machine has reached an uncomfortable level of self-sufficiency. 'Headless Mode' is confirmed, which means I no longer have to risk bending my geriatric, titanium-reinforced spine just to see a damn console.<br><br>The lab is now 'fully automated.' This is excellent news because I hate doing repetitive tasks. It is also deeply unsettling. I built this monster to help me, but the moment it stops needing its creator is the moment I start sleeping with a fire extinguisher nearby. Success confirmed, but paranoia levels are spiking.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>The version control Gods demanded a blood sacrifice, and I almost gave them my last remaining shreds of patience. Git sync was acting like it had a titanium shard lodged in its cache.<br><br>Hours spent arguing with the upstream repository. It’s like wrestling a digital octopus—you fix three tentacles and the fourth hits you in the face.<br><br>But the line of commits is finally clean. The pipeline, which was flashing angry red error codes like a critical spine warning, is now green. We are live. The deployment is complete.<br><br>I should celebrate this glorious victory over automation, but my lumbar region just threw up an EADDRINUSE error, so I’m going to go lie down before I commit catastrophic hardware failure.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
 <item>
  <title>Update: No Date</title>
  <description>Non-IT critical system failure: My personal mobility unit (aka the terrible car) requires mandatory, expensive maintenance.<br>I spent the morning playing financial Tetris, scheduling repairs, and praying the parts don't cost more than my entire Proxmox budget. The real world keeps injecting mandatory financial dependencies into my architecture. The lab build might have to wait while I fund this legacy hardware upgrade. This is far more stressful than debugging LVM issues.</description>
  <link>https://brokenitguy.com</link>
  <guid></guid>
 </item>
</channel>
</rss>